jordans.co.uk 2008-05-16

# Jordans International Limited privacy policy

|  |   |   
  
---|---|---  
  |    
**Jordans International Limited**  
**Privacy policy**  
****  
Jordans International Limited recognises that your privacy is important, and is committed to protecting it. This document sets out our policy in relation to any personal information which you supply to us through your use of this website.By providing your personal information through this website you agree to the collection, storage and use of your personal information by us in accordance with this Privacy Policy.If we change this policy we will post changes on this page so that you are always aware of them. By continuing to use this website after such changes have been posted you will be deemed to have accepted and consented to them, whether you revisit this page or not.

**The information which we collect**

You may browse our web site without disclosing personal data. However, if you register, and / or order products from us by completing our online forms or contact us by e-mail, we will collect the following personal information from you:  

  * your name, postal address, organisation name, e-mail address, telephone number, facsimile number 

so that we can fulfil your order and contact you in case there is a query with your order.Where you order from us, we may also collect:  

  * your debit or credit card number, expiry date and other relevant information to allow us to collect payment 

so we can process and fulfil your order.

**How we use your personal information**

In addition to providing our services and products to you as set out above, we will also use your information for market research purposes and credit control purposes.We may also use this information to notify you about our services and products, legal developments and training sessions or events which we believe may be of interest to you.If you do not wish to receive such information, please write to the Head of Marketing, Jordans Limited, 21 St Thomas Street, Bristol BS1 6JS, marking your envelope "Data Protection".

**How we share your personal information**

We may share your personal information with other companies in our group, including, Jordans Limited, Jordans Publishing Limited, Jordans (Scotland) Limited and our overseas offices (full details of which are available on our [website](http://www.jordans.co.uk/jordans3.nsf/Main/International+home)[](http://www.jordans-international.co.uk/)), for any of the above purposes and with those with whom we are co-presenting any training session or event (in which case the use by our co-presenters will be restricted to arranging and publicising the event). In order to provide services to you we may be required to pass your personal information to parties located outside of the European Economic Area in countries which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in the UK. Where this is the case we will take reasonable steps to ensure the privacy of your information.Except in the situations listed above or as required by law or other regulation, we will not pass, disclose, rent or sell your personal information (other than any personal information which is already publicly available and which is incorporated into our search products) to any third party without your prior written consent.

**Protecting your information**

When you order from us we use a secure server. All personal and credit card information is encrypted using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology before it is sent to us over the internet.We have a Data Protection Policy and strict internal procedures designed to protect your personal information from unauthorised access, improper use, alteration, unintended destruction or other loss.

**Cookies**

Cookies are small files which some websites transfer onto the hard drive of your computer. Cookies store information so that you are recognised the next time that you visit the site or to process your order. You can set your web browser to prevent it from automatically accepting cookies or to notify you before a cookie is accepted.  
  
This site uses cookies only for the duration of your session to store information relevant to any order you may place with us. If you have disabled cookies you may need to adjust the privacy settings on your internet browser to use this site. Further information on this can usually be found in the help menu of your internet browser.

**Accessing personal data**

You have the right, by written request and on payment of a small fee, to a copy of any personal data (as defined in the Data Protection Act 1998) which we hold about you. |   |    
|   |   
  
| 

| **

Contacts

** |   
---|---|---  
| 

For further information, please contact our [customer services](mailto:customerservices@jordans-international.com).  
  
Jordans International Limited  
21 St Thomas Street, Bristol BS1 6JS  
Tel: 0117 923 0600  
Fax: 0117 923 0063  
DX 78161 Bristol  

20-22 Bedford Row, London WC1R 4JS  
Tel: 020 7400 3333  
Fax: 020 7400 3366  
DX 1016 Lon/Ch'ry Ln  

|   
|  |  |  |   
  
| **

Legal notices

** |   
---|---|---  
| 

**Jordans International Limited**

|   
|  |  |  |
